<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Netmiko.com</title>
	<atom:link href="https://netmiko.com/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://netmiko.com</link>
	<description>News &#38; Tech</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:42:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Python Program to Find the Sum of Squares of Digits of a Number</title>
		<link>https://netmiko.com/python-program-to-find-the-sum-of-squares-of-digits-of-a-number/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aomi Bora]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://netmiko.com/?p=6604</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This article presents a Python program for finding and printing the sum of the squares of the digits of a number entered by the user. Python Program to Find the]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This article presents a Python program for finding and printing the sum of the squares of the digits of a number entered by the user. This code prompts the user to enter a number and stores it in a variable called . It then initializes a variable called to the value of and another variable called to 0. It enters a while loop that continues executing as long as is not equal to 0.</p>
<p><a href="https://netmiko.com/python-program-to-find-the-sum-of-squares-of-digits-of-a-number/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Python Program to Find Product of Mid Digits</title>
		<link>https://netmiko.com/python-program-to-find-product-of-mid-digits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aomi Bora]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://netmiko.com/?p=6602</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This article presents a Python program for finding and printing the product of the middle digits of a number entered by the user at runtime. For example, if the user]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This article presents a Python program for finding and printing the product of the middle digits of a number entered by the user at runtime. For example, if the user enters the number 2351, the output will be the product of the middle digits, which is 3 * 5, or 15. This code prompts the user to enter a number and stores it in a variable called . It then initializes a variable called to the value...</p>
<p><a href="https://netmiko.com/python-program-to-find-product-of-mid-digits/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Python Program to Find Sum of First and Last Digit</title>
		<link>https://netmiko.com/python-program-to-find-sum-of-first-and-last-digit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aomi Bora]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://netmiko.com/?p=6600</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This article presents some Python programs for finding and printing the sum of the first and last digits of a number entered by the user at runtime. For example, if]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This article presents some Python programs for finding and printing the sum of the first and last digits of a number entered by the user at runtime. For example, if the user enters the number 2493, the output will be the sum of the first digit (2) and the last digit (3), which is 5. This code prompts the user to enter a number and stores it in a variable called . It then initializes a variable...</p>
<p><a href="https://netmiko.com/python-program-to-find-sum-of-first-and-last-digit/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Python Programs to Find Sum of Digits of a Number</title>
		<link>https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-find-sum-of-digits-of-a-number/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aomi Bora]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://netmiko.com/?p=6598</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to find and print the sum of the digits of a number entered by the user at runtime using four different approaches in]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this article, you will learn how to find and print the sum of the digits of a number entered by the user at runtime using four different approaches in Python: a while loop, a for loop, a function, and a class. For example, if the user enters the number 123, the output will be 1 + 2 + 3, which is 6. This code prompts the user to enter a number and stores it in a variable called .</p>
<p><a href="https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-find-sum-of-digits-of-a-number/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Python Programs to Count Digits in a Number</title>
		<link>https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-count-digits-in-a-number/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aomi Bora]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://netmiko.com/?p=6596</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This article presents two Python programs for counting the total number of digits in a given number. The first program uses a while loop, and the second program uses the]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This article presents two Python programs for counting the total number of digits in a given number. The first program uses a while loop, and the second program uses the built-in function. For example, if the user inputs the number 1234, the output will be 4 because the number contains 4 digits. This code prompts the user to enter a number and stores it in a variable called . It then initializes a...</p>
<p><a href="https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-count-digits-in-a-number/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Python Programs to Reverse a Number</title>
		<link>https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-reverse-a-number/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aomi Bora]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://netmiko.com/?p=6594</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This article presents five approaches in Python for finding and printing the reverse of a number entered by the user. The first approach uses a while loop, the second uses]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This article presents five approaches in Python for finding and printing the reverse of a number entered by the user. The first approach uses a while loop, the second uses a for loop, the third uses a list, the fourth uses a function, and the fifth uses recursion. This code prompts the user to enter a number and stores it in a variable called . It then initializes a variable called to 0 and a...</p>
<p><a href="https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-reverse-a-number/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Python Programs to Check Perfect Number</title>
		<link>https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-check-perfect-number/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aomi Bora]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://netmiko.com/?p=6592</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This article has two Python programs for checking whether a number entered by the user is a perfect number. The first program uses a for loop, and the second program]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This article has two Python programs for checking whether a number entered by the user is a perfect number. The first program uses a for loop, and the second program uses a while loop. This code prompts the user to enter a number and stores it in a variable called . It then initializes a variable called to 0. Next, it enters a for loop that iterates over the range of numbers from 1 to .</p>
<p><a href="https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-check-perfect-number/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Python Programs to Check Palindrome Number</title>
		<link>https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-check-palindrome-number/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aomi Bora]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 03:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://netmiko.com/?p=6568</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In this article, we provide three Python programs that determine if a user-entered number is a palindrome number. The first program is a simple implementation, while the second uses a]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this article, we provide three Python programs that determine if a user-entered number is a palindrome number. The first program is a simple implementation, while the second uses a function, and the third uses a class. Before discussing the programs, let&rsquo;s quickly define what a palindrome number is. A palindrome number is a number that is equal to its reverse. For example, the number 121 is a...</p>
<p><a href="https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-check-palindrome-number/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Python Programs to Check Armstrong Number</title>
		<link>https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-check-armstrong-number/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aomi Bora]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 03:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://netmiko.com/?p=6566</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In this article, we provide three Python programs that determine if a user-entered number is an Armstrong number. The first program is a simple implementation, while the second uses a]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this article, we provide three Python programs that determine if a user-entered number is an Armstrong number. The first program is a simple implementation, while the second uses a user-defined function, and the third uses a class. This program prompts the user to enter a number, which is then stored in the variable. The value of is then stored in a temporary variable and the number of digits...</p>
<p><a href="https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-check-armstrong-number/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Python Programs to Check Positive, Negative or Zero</title>
		<link>https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-check-positive-negative-or-zero/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aomi Bora]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 03:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://netmiko.com/?p=6564</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In this article, we have examined several Python programs that determine whether a number entered by the user is positive, negative, or zero. The programs include: A simple program that]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this article, we have examined several Python programs that determine whether a number entered by the user is positive, negative, or zero. The programs include: A simple program that checks if a number is positive, zero, or negative A program that uses a function to check if a number is positive, zero, or negative A program that uses a class to check if a number is positive, zero...</p>
<p><a href="https://netmiko.com/python-programs-to-check-positive-negative-or-zero/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
